10khits.com 2018-12-28

# Terms and Privacy | 10KHits

##  Terms of Use 

###  I. Overview 

Our (“Service”, “Website” or “Application”) is a traffic exchange service provided by 10KHits LLC (“Company”) that provides individuals and businesses access to fast and scalable web hits through our exchanger application. The service includes the web site at [www.10khits.com](http://www.10khits.com/) (“Website” or “Site”) which has a collection of resources related to 10KHits’ common questions, search engine marketing, search engine optimization, social media marketing, website performance and digital analytics in the knowledge base. The Company may change the Service from time to time, with or without notice, by adding, modifying, suspending, or discontinuing features of the Service. 

You may access the Service or Site as a free or paid user (“User” or “Subscriber”). The Company reserves the right to charge fees for upgrades and change the price of any service upgrades associated with the Site or Service at any time without notice. 

10KHits reserves the right to cancel, suspend or block access of Users to the Site or Service at its sole discretion for violation of our terms or for any other reason without notification. 

###  II. Conditions Governing All Users 

In no way are we considered an investment to earn money online or a pay-per-click program where users are paid to click on banner ads. We do not payout for your traffic points that you have accumulated from surfing on our network. We only provide commission traffic points that you earn from surfing as well as from referrals that you have collected with your unique referral link. Your traffic points may be used to send visits back to your own websites, blogs, videos, etc.

  * We cannot be held liable for any content displayed or damages (malicious scripts, viruses, malware and other damages) that might be caused directly or indirectly through the Traffic Exchange system or by utilizing this service.
  * The Service is available to Users who are human and who are 18 years of age or older. 
  * Users who are Subscribers must be at least 18 years old.
  * A valid email address must be used for your account.
  * Users who sign up may receive emails, newsletters and updates from 10KHits.
  * Users may not impersonate any person, brand or entity on the Site.
  * Do not add websites to the network that you do not own or have permission to.
  * You agree to inform 10KHits of any security breach or bugs you encounter from the use of the Service or Site.
  * We are not responsible for the content visible on our Users websites which may have been falsely marked as Safe for Work that includes nudity, violence, pornography or profanity.
  * We are not responsible for any audio, music or sound that is played from Users websites while you surf on our network. It is the responsibility of the user to mute their devices while surfing.
  * We do not tolerate profanity or abusive language in any form of contact with us including, but not limited to, emails or support ticket system. Such behavior will result in a warning, followed by suspension and/or termination if the warning is not heeded.
  * We make no guarantees for the number of hits (results) that will be registered on third-party services and third-party tools.

###  III. Conditions Governing Subscribers 

Any User who has purchased an upgrade that is currently active will be referred to as a “Subscriber”. As a Subscriber, you must agree to the payment terms presented here before you subscribe to the Service. 

Subscribers are responsible for taking actions prior to the renewal of their subscriptions if the Subscriber does not wish to renew automatically. The Company may not send out future notifications or invoices of your renewal and it is your sole responsibility to check the Billing History of your account. Subscriptions recur monthly and can be unsubscribed to from your PayPal account. 

**30-Day Money Back Guarantee Policy.** The Company will allow 100% refunds to Subscribers who have purchased upgrades or booster packs within the past 30 days with the exception of: 

  * recurring payments
  * payments made with promotional codes
  * bulk order payments (custom packages)
  * abusing our service(s) which includes:
    * using more than 80% of your purchased points from upgrades or boosters
  * using different merchant accounts to purchase for the same 10KHits account
  * cryptocurrency payments are NON-REFUNDABLE (Bitcoin, Bitcoin Cash, Ethereum, Litecoin, etc.)

The Company reserves the right to refuse refunds or give customers a partial refund after the 30 day period has past. 

Any threat of legal action against 10KHits by a client will result in immediate account and service termination without refund.

###  IV. Acceptable Use Policy 

Users are obligated to follow the acceptable use policy regarding User Websites. All websites added to the Service or Site by Users shall be referred to as “User Websites”. 

  * Users assume legal responsibility for all User Websites.
  * Users agree that no copyright, trademark, privacy rights or other intellectual property rights are being violated by adding the websites to your account via the Site or Service.
  * Users agree not to add websites that they do not have permission to add on the Site.
  * Users will not add websites that can harm or transmit viruses/malware to computers or other devices when visited.
  * Users agree to mark all User Websites that contains nudity, violence, pornography or profanity as NSFW (Not Safe For Work) in the manage site settings.
  * Users under the age of 18 may not enable the "View Not Safe For Work pages?" setting in the user settings.

Violation of our AUP may result in legal action for damages, issue warnings, website suspensions or the termination/suspension of your account. 

###  V. Service Limitations 

10KHits may have limitations concerning use of Service including by way of example the maximum hits per hour that you set in your account may not be reached due to low network activity during the hour. 10KHits reserves the right to discontinue any of its features or its entire service at any time without notice. You agree that 10KHits will not be liable to you or to any third party for any modification or discontinuation of its features or the Service. 

###  VI. Points 

10KHits offer points to users and subscribers for different activities they partake in. Each point is worth a 10 second hit. For example, a 60 second hit would use up 6 points. By using our exchanger and surfing, you’ll earn points for your account. You may also buy points by upgrading your account, purchasing booster packs for extra points or our promo offers. Points are non-transferable and cannot be traded from one account to another. 

###  VII. Proprietary Rights 

10KHits respects the intellectual property of others and we ask the Users to do the same. The digital images and graphics found on the Site are copyright to their respective owners. 

Users may not modify, reproduce, distribute, publicly display 10KHits’ content in whole or in part unless authorized by 10KHits or its respective owners. 

###  VIII. Digital Millennium Copyright Act 

If you believe that images or photos hosted on this website infringes upon any copyright which you own or control, you may send a written notification of such infringement as set forth below:

By email: [[email protected]](https://www.10khits.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#1e7d71706a7f7d6a5e2f2e7576776a6d307d7173)

In your notification you must include the following: 

  1. Identification of the copyrighted work or works claimed to have been infringed;
  2. Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit us to locate the material;
  3. Information sufficient to permit us to contact the complaining party (e.g. telephone number, an electronic mail address);
  4. A statement that the complaining party has a good-faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent or the law; and
  5. A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.

Upon receipt of notice as described above, 10KHits will take the appropriate action at its sole discretion, including removal of the challenged use from the Service or Site. 

###  IX. Liability Limitation 

You acknowledge that 10KHits cannot provide the Service at a reasonable price without limiting its liability as set forth herein, so, as an express condition of use of the Site or Service, you agree to limit 10KHits’ potential liability to you as described in this clause.

10KHits does not:

  1. Guarantee the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of any information on the Site or Service on the Website.
  2. Adopt, endorse or accept responsibility for the accuracy or reliability of any opinion, advice, or statement made by any party that appears on the Site.
  3. 10KHits and its partners will not be responsible for any loss or damage resulting from your reliance on information or other content found on the Site.

You hereby agree that you will indemnify 10KHits, its officers, employees and agents, from and against any and all claims, demands, actions, losses, liabilities, costs and expenses arising from any breach or alleged breach of any term, warranty or condition of this agreement, or from any claims of infringement or alleged infringement arising from your access or misuse of the website or violation of our terms of use. 

###  X. Other Clauses 

**Electronic Form.** By accessing the Site or Service, you consent to have this Agreement provided to you in electronic form. Please print this form for your record. 

**Updates.** 10KHits reserves the right to make modifications and updates to the site that may change the appearance or the functionality of the Site entirely without any notifications. 

###  XI. Class Action Waiver 

THERE WILL BE NO RIGHT OR AUTHORITY FOR ANY DISPUTE TO BE BROUGHT, HEARD, OR ARBITRATED AS A CLASS ACTION (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION OPT OUT CLASS ACTIONS OR OPT IN COLLECTIVE CLASS ACTIONS), OR IN A REPRESENTATIVE OR PRIVATE ATTORNEY GENERAL CAPACITY ON BEHALF OF A CLASS OF PERSONS OR THE GENERAL PUBLIC.  ALL DISPUTES SHALL BE RESOLVED ON AN INDIVIDUAL BASIS ONLY.

**If you have questions about this agreement, email:[ [email protected]](https://www.10khits.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#6a0905041e0b091e2a5b5a0102031e1944090507)**

**_Last modified: May 3, 2018_**

##  Privacy Policy 

###  I. Introduction 

10KHits (“Company”, “10KHits”, or “We”) understand that your privacy is very important to you and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. 

You can be assured that your personal information will only be used in accordance with this policy. 

10KHits may change this policy from time to time by updating this page without any notice. You should check this page regularly to ensure that you are up to date with the latest privacy policy. The date of which the policy was last modified will be listed at the top of the page for your reference. 

###  II. Children Under the Age of 13 

Our Site is not intended for children under the age of 13. Anyone under 13 may not provide any personal information on the Site. We do not knowingly collect personal data from minors. If you are under the age of 13, please avoid using the Site and do not provide any information to the Site. 

###  III. Information We Collect About You 

Our website collects information about our Users. We may collect the following types of information: 

  1. **Information You Provide**

We collect information by which you may be personally identified such as full name, email address and country. This information is collected directly from you when you provide it to us when signing up for an account or changing your account settings. 

  2. **Cookies, IP Addresses and Log Information**

As you interact with and use the Site, Service or application, we may automatically collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns including traffic data, location data, details about your visit and site usage logs. We may also collect information about your computer or device, internet connection, IP address, operating system and browser type.

The technology we use to automatically collect your data and keep you logged in may include cookies, flash cookies or web beacons. 

  3. **Data Collected from Social Media Pages and Lead Ads**

All data collected from Lead Ads on Facebook, Twitter and other social media pages owned and managed by 10KHits may be used to create a new account for the user and also subscribe the user to 10KHits newsletters. We may occasionally send out promotional e-mails to our users.

In addition to using cookies and related technologies as described above, we also may permit certain third party companies to help us tailor advertising that we think may be of interest to users and to collect and use other data about user activities on our Sites and/or Services (e.g., to allow them to tailor ads on third party services). These companies may deliver ads that might also place cookies and otherwise track user behavior.

For example, we may use Google’s “remarketing” service to target our ads to you based on your prior use of the Site when you visit on other sites in Google’s content network.

###  IV. How We Use Your Information 

We use the information we collect from you or that you provided to us: 

  * To provide you with information about other services that may interest you based on your previous purchases
  * To deliver relevant advertising to you through social media ads such as Facebook
  * To administer our site including troubleshooting, data analysis and statistical purposes to keep our site safe and secure
  * To manage and operate your account with us
  * To present User Websites to you and other Users based on location
  * To determine your geolocation by country code
  * To provide you with information or content tailored to you
  * To inform you about our blog posts, updates, latest offers and newsletters
  * To alert you of Site or Service changes
  * To notify you about your account or subscription
  * To make website analysis for web marketing and service improvements
  * To provide you with customer service via support ticket system
  * To analyze websites, files and other content you submit through Google Safe Browsing service
  * In the event of payment disputes
  * For any other purpose with your consent

We will never sell your personal information to third parties. 

###  V. Disclosure of Your Information 

We may share your personal information to advertisers and advertising networks and other third parties that require data to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others.

Re-Targeting: We partner with third parties to display advertising on our Sites and manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partners may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this Site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. The only way to completely “opt out” of the collection of any information through cookies or other tracking technology is to actively manage the settings on your browser or mobile device. Please refer to your browser’s or mobile device’s technical information for instructions on how to delete and disable cookies, and other tracking/recording tools (to learn more about cookies, clear gifs/web beacons and related technologies, you may wish to visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and/or the Network Advertising Initiative’s online resources, at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)). If you access the 10KHits Service or Sites on your mobile device, you may not be able to control tracking technologies through the settings. 

Malware Protection: When you add your websites to 10KHits, we may communicate with Google Safe Browsing service to verify the potential risks of your websites. In these cases, 10KHits will submit some information about your website including website details and URL to Google Safe Browsing service to determine whether or not the website should be blocked for having harmful content such as malware.

The Google Privacy Policy explains how Google handles collected data: <https://policies.google.com/privacy>

Payments & Disputes: We use third party payment processors to process all payments made to us. In connection with the processing of such payments, we do not store any personally identifiable information or any financial information such as credit card numbers or bank accounts on our Website. All such information is provided directly to and stored by our third party payment processors: PayPal, Stripe and Coinbase Commerce.

PayPal, Stripe and Coinbase Commerce have their privacy policies which can be viewed at the following links: <https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full> <https://stripe.com/us/privacy](https://stripe.com/us/privacy> <https://commerce.coinbase.com/legal/privacy-policy/>

We may also disclose Personal Information collected on this Website to our third party payment processors to resolve payment disputes.

We may collect and disclose anonymous and aggregated information of Users without restriction for the purpose of product research, improvement of Service and other commercial purposes.

We may also disclose your personal information to comply with any court order, or legal process, including responding to any government or regulatory request. 

###  VI. Updating Your Information 

You can update any of your personal information including your password by logging into the Site and visiting the settings page. If you would like to remove your personal information from the Site or close your account, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://www.10khits.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#dab9b5b4aebbb9ae9aebeab1b2b3aea9f4b9b5b7). 

###  VII. Linking Your Gravatar 

You agree to give permission to 10KHits to use your Gravatar on the website and to display the image as your account’s avatar for the Site. You can change or delete your Gravatar at any time by going to [https://www.gravatar.com](https://www.gravatar.com/). 

###  VIII. Security Disclaimer 

We have implemented several security measures to protect your personal information from becoming loss or stolen from unauthorized Users. Our site uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) for communication security over the internet. All information you provide to us is stored in a database within a state-of-the-art data center. We do not store any payment login information such as your PayPal username/passwords however we do collect transaction ids of your purchases on the Site. 

The information that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored in, a country outside the European Economic Area (EEA) and/or United Kingdom (UK). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA or UK who work for us or for one of our suppliers. The laws in some countries may not provide as much legal protection for your information as in the EEA. By submitting your personal information, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy. 

The security of your data also depends on you. You are responsible for keeping your password confidential. It is also recommended to not use the same password you have used on other websites. We will never ask for your password so be careful about giving this information out in public areas like message boards. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not 100% secure. We cannot guarantee the security of your data on the Site as it may be vulnerable to hackers or hardware failure. Although we do backup our database regularly, any transmission of personal data is at your own risk. 10KHits will not be responsible for any damages done. 

###  IX. Cookies 

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This ensures you get the best experience on our website and to provide interest-based advertising. You may adjust the settings on your browser to refuse cookies but some of the services on our website(s) may not work if you do so. 

###  X. Data Access, Correction, Deletion, Opt Out 

You have the right to access or change certain personal information held about you by 10KHits LLC. At any time, you have the right to access or correct inaccurate data such as Display Name and E-mail Address within the settings page here: <https://www.10khits.com/dashboard/settings>

We use third party advertisers to serve relevant ads to you and to measure the effectiveness of such advertisements. These ad providers provide information on how to opt out on their websites. Use of these technologies by our Ad providers are subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our privacy policy.

You have the right to opt out of our marketing and system newsletters within the settings page. From time to time we may e-mail you system alerts, special offers, discounts and promo codes for our services. You can exercise your right to not receive these e-mails by ticking or unticking the "Subscribe to Newsletters" or "Subscribe to System Alerts" boxes here: <https://www.10khits.com/dashboard/settings>

You can also close your account using the close your account link in the settings page however your personal information will still be stored on our servers. To delete personal information about you that is stored on our servers, you may send a request to [[email protected]](https://www.10khits.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#0d6e6263796c6e794d3c3d666564797e236e6260).

If you are a resident of the EEA, you have the following data protection rights, which you may exercise by contacting us via support ticket:

  * Right to Access - You have the right to access your personal data and to request a data export from us.
  * Right to Rectification - You have the right to have any incorrect or incomplete personal data corrected.
  * Right to Restrict - You have the right to request the restriction of processing your personal data where there is no legitimate reason for us to do so.
  * Right to Object - You have the right to object to the processing of your personal data where we have no legitimate reason to do so.
  * Right to Erasure - You have the right to request the erasure of any personal data we have collected. However, this right does not override our financial and legal requirements to keep certain data (see above).
  * Right to Withdraw Consent - You have the right to withdraw consent (unsubscribe) from any marketing communications we may send you.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

**If you have any concerns about our privacy policy, please e-mail[ [email protected]](https://www.10khits.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#c5a6aaabb1a4a6b185f4f5aeadacb1b6eba6aaa8)**

**_Last modified: May 24, 2018_**
